<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quotes>
	<quote>
		<author>Aerosmith</author>
		<cite>Life's a journey, not a destination.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Albert Einstein</author>
		<cite>Only two things are infinite, the universe and human stupidity, and I'm not sure about the former.</cite>
		<cite>Great spirits have always encountered violent opposition from mediocre minds.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Allen Ng</author>
		<cite>If you ask a stupid question, you'll get an answer, stupid.</cite>
		<cite>I hear the collapse of our civilization in the sounds heard at the grocery store, not in the screams of children, but in the silence of adults.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>American Indian Proverb</author>
		<cite>Listen or thy tongue will keep thee deaf.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Anne McCaffrey</author>
		<cite>[They] never discovered and eventually forgot to ask.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Aristotle</author>
		<cite>We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence then, is not an act, but a habit.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Astragarl Hornwood</author>
		<cite>Dragons?  Splendid things lad--so long as you only look at them in tapestries, or the masks worn at revels, or from about three realms off...</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Bob Marley</author>
		<cite>No woman, No cry.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Chad Mitchell</author>
		<cite>Hey! These things--they happen sometimes.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Charlie Parker</author>
		<cite>Music is your own experience, your thoughts, your wisdom. If you don't live it, it won't come out of your horn.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Chinese Proverb</author>
		<cite>Teachers open the door, but you must enter by yourself.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>David Hockney</author>
		<cite>Art has to move you and design does not, unless it's a good design for a bus.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>George Bernard Shaw</author>
		<cite>Liberty means responsibility. That is why most men dread it.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Georges Bidault</author>
		<cite>The weak have one weapon: the errors of those who they think are strong.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Hebrews 9:27a</author>
		<cite>It is appointed once for a man to die...</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>James Branch Cabell</author>
		<cite>Mundus Vult Decipi (The world wants to be deceived.)</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>John Stallworthy</author>
		<cite>They stand most straight who learn to walk beneath a weight.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Johnathan Swift</author>
		<cite>When a true genius appears in the world, you may know him by this sign, that the dunces are all in confederacy against him.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Juvenal</author>
		<cite>If you've run out of luck, it doesn't matter how long your penis is.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Louie Armstrong when asked "What is jazz?":</author>
		<cite>If you have to ask, you'll never know.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author><i>Al Pacino as</i> Lowell Bergman</author>
		<cite>Ordinary people under extraordinary stress, Mike.  What'd the hell you expect?  Grace and consistency?</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Mark Twain</author>
		<cite>Keep away from people who try to belittle your ambitions. Small people always do that, but the really great make you feel that you, too, can become great.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>R.A. Salvatore</author>
		<cite>If a person needs proof of a god's existence, then the very notion of spirituality is diminished into sensuality and we have reduced what is holy into what is logical.</cite>
		<cite>I need no fantasies to belittle the great treasures that I already possess.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Rodger Hanson</author>
		<cite>Right Sailor, Right Place, Wrong Software</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>The Eagles</author>
		<cite>Somtimes to keep it together you gotta leave it alone.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>The Tyranny of the Diploma--Forbes Magazine</author>
		<cite>Time was when a high school diploma was pretty good proof that the holder had received a basic education.  No more.  Too many high schools certify kids who can barely read or reckon, with the result that employers today want to see a college diploma as evidence of basic literacy.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>unknown</author>
		<cite>If you would ever like to go into a cave, I will take you. If you are curious about a dungeon, I'll find you a book on the subject.</cite>
		<cite>The world is so fast that there are days when the person who says it can't be done is interrupted by the person who is doing it.</cite>
		<cite>"I think not!" retorted Descartes and promptly disappeared.</cite>
		<cite>Light travels faster than sound, that's why some people seem bright until they talk.</cite>
		<cite>Habit is the ballast that chains a dog to his vomit.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Van Ledbetter</author>
		<cite>There's a lot of times when you can't save money and save souls at the same time.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Yogi Berra</author>
		<cite>If you don't know where you're going, you'll end up somewhere else.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Dave Butler</author>
		<cite>Silly is a state of Mind; Stupid is a way of Life.</cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Ian Lawuf</author>
		<cite>I feel like Joe Pelton playing Go Fish!</cite>
		<cite><![CDATA[My name is Ian Lawuf and I Am No Longer Afiliated With U F*@&s]]></cite>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<author>Scott Adams</author>
		<cite>If there are no stupid questions, then what kind of questions do stupid people ask?  Do they get smart just in time to ask questions?</cite>
	</quote>
</quotes>
